// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Igneous rocks are strong because of their",
    answer: "D. Interlocking grain textures",
    options: [
      "A. Temperature",
      "B. Color",
      "C. Water Content",
      "D. Interlocking grain textures",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "A rock is a natural solid earth material made up of _____.",
    answer: "C. Minerals",
    options: [
      "A. Rocks",
      "B. Glaciers",
      "C. Minerals",
      "D. Hummus",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The pressure required for metamorphism can be generated by",
    answer: "A. Pressure from weight of overlying rock.",
    options: [
      "A. Pressure from weight of overlying rock.",
      "B. Hydrothermal solutions",
      "C. Cementation and lithification",
      "D. Heat from magma bodies in touch with surrounding rock",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The name rock is given when it is broken down to smaller pieces.",
    answer: "C. Weathering",
    options: [
      "A. Texture",
      "B. Sediment",
      "C. Weathering",
      "D. Erosion",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The series of processes in which rock changes from one type to another.",
    answer: "D. Rock Cycle",
    options: [
      "A. Rock transformation",
      "B. Lithification",
      "C. Sedimentation",
      "D. Rock Cycle",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What type of heat transfer occurs when there is rising of warm air currents?",
    answer: "C. Convection",
    options: [
      "A. Radiation",
      "B. Conduction",
      "C. Convection",
      "D. None of the Above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the definition of CONDUCTION?",
    answer: "B. When heat transfers from objects that are touching.",
    options: [
      "A. When heat is transferred through waves of heat across a distance.",
      "B. When heat transfers from objects that are touching.",
      "C. When heat is transferred through circulation of liquid or gases.",
      "D. All of the Above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "During convection, hot substances _________ while cooler substances_______________.",
    answer: "B. Rise, sink",
    options: [
      "A. Rise, remains at rest",
      "B. Rise, sink",
      "C. Sink, rise",
      "D. Sink, remains at rest",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "From deep within the Earth, molten magma bubbles up heating rocks that surround it. This process turns igneous and sedimentary rocks:",
    answer: "D. Metamorphic rocks",
    options: [
      "A. Genesis",
      "B. Slate",
      "C. Marble",
      "D. Metamorphic rocks",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What do you call a rigid substance composed of one or more minerals?",
    answer: "B. Rock",
    options: [
      "A. Solid",
      "B. Rock",
      "C. Earth surface",
      "D. Particles",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "This is a type of rock that results from the cooling of the magma.",
    answer: "A. Igneous",
    options: [
      "A. Igneous",
      "B. Metamorphic",
      "C. Sedimentary",
      "D. None of the Above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "These are rocks that are changed by temperature, pressure, and hot liquids.",
    answer: "B. Metamorphic",
    options: [
      "A. Igneous",
      "B. Metamorphic",
      "C. Sedimentary",
      "D. None of the Above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "It is called a molten rock below the surface of the Earth",
    answer: "B. Magma",
    options: [
      "A. Lava",
      "B. Magma",
      "C. Rocks",
      "D. Minerals",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which layer of the Earth do convection currents occur in?",
    answer: "C. Mantle",
    options: [
      "A. Crust",
      "B. Outer Core",
      "C. Mantle",
      "D. Inner Core",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "These are geologic processes that occur beneath the surface of the Earth.",
    answer: "B. Endogenic",
    options: [
      "A. Earthquake",
      "B. Endogenic",
      "C. Exogenic",
      "D. Tectonism",
    ],
  },
];
